Papers of the International Labor Defense on Microfilm 5815 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 0036. Box 18/Folder f6. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 73 pages., 1934; 2 (Reel 17)
  August-November 1934
- 0109. Box 18/Folder f7. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 46 pages., 1935; 3 (Reel 17)
  January-July 1935
- 0155. Box 18/Folder f8. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 47 pages., 1935; 4 (Reel 17)
- 0202. Box 18/Folder f9. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 68 pages., 1935; 5 (Reel 17)
- 0270. Box 18/Folder f10. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 106 pages., 1935; 6 (Reel 17)
  November-December 1935
- 0376. Box 18/Folder f11. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 37 pages., 1936; 7 (Reel 17)
  January-June 1936
- 0413. Box 18/Folder f12. Angelo Herndon Case. Magazine Articles. 35 pages., 1934-1935; 8 (Reel 17)
- 0448. Box 18/Folder f13. Angelo Herndon Case. Editorials and Cartoons. 101 pages., 1935; 9 (Reel 17)
- 0549. Box 18/Folder f14. Angelo Herndon Case. Editorials and Cartoons. 17 pages., 1936; 10 (Reel 17)
- 0566. Box 18/Folder f15. Angelo Herndon Case. Editorials and Cartoons. 44 pages., 1937; 11 (Reel 17)
- 0610. Box 19/Folder f16. Angelo Herndon Case. Press Release - International Labor Defense Press Service. 67 pages., 1932-1934; 12 (Reel 17)
- 0677. Box 19/Folder f17. Angelo Herndon Case. Press Release - International Labor Defense Press Service. 95 pages., 1935; 13 (Reel 17)
  April-July 1935
- 0772. Box 19/Folder f18. Angelo Herndon Case. Press Release - International Labor Defense Press Service. 59 pages., 1935; 14 (Reel 17)
  August-September 1935
- 0831. Box 19/Folder f19. Angelo Herndon Case. Press Release - International Labor Defense Press Service. 67 pages., 1935; 15 (Reel 17)
- 0872. Box 19/Folder f20. Angelo Herndon Case. Press Release - International Labor Defense Press Service. 16 pages., 1936; 16 (Reel 17)
- 0888. Box 19/Folder f21. Angelo Herndon Case. Press Release - International Labor Defense Press Service. 13 pages., 1937; 17 (Reel 17)
- 0901. Box 19/Folder f22. Angelo Herndon Case. Herndon v. Georgia - South Eastern Reporter. 116 pages., 1934; 18 (Reel 17)
- 1017. Box 19/Folder f23. Angelo Herndon Case. Eighteen Others [in similar cases]. 35 pages., 1934-1935; 19 (Reel 17)
- 1018. Box 19/Folder f23. Angelo Herndon Case. Partial Transcript of Testimony. Georgia v. Annie Leathers and Leah Young. Fulton County Superior Court, Georgia. 4 pages., 1934; 20 (Reel 17)
- 1052. Box 19/Folder f24. Angelo Herndon Case. United States Supreme Court Decision - Press Releases. 14 pages., 1937; 21 (Reel 17)
- 0001. Box 19/Folder f25. Angelo Herndon Case. United States supreme Court Decision - Telegrams and News clippings. 114 pages., 1935-1937; 1 (Reel 18)
- 0115. Box 19/Folder f26. Angelo Herndon Case. United States Supreme Court Decision - Telegrams and News clippings. 11 pages., 1935-1937; 2 (Reel 18)
- 0226. Box 19/Folder f27. Angelo Herndon Case. Publicity Material - Releases, Instructions, Case Information, Petitions, etcetera. 10 pages., 1934; 3 (Reel 18)
- 0236. Box 19/Folder f28. Angelo Herndon Case. Joint Committee to Aid the Herndon Defense - Releases, Minutes, Publicity, etcetera. 26 pages., 1935-1936; 4 (Reel 18)
  [September 1935-October 1936]
- 0262. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. 102 pages., 1926-1942; 5 (Reel 18)
- 0264. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents - An Act Defining Sedition and Prescribing the Punishment Therefore, State of Georgia. 3 pages., 1866; 6 (Reel 18)
- 0267. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents - Verbatim Quotations from the Herndon Record. 4 pages., 1933; 7 (Reel 18)
  January 16, 1933
- 0271. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents - Correspondence. 6 pages., 1939-1942; 8 (Reel 18)
- 0278. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents - Herndon v. Georgia. United States Supreme Court. 15 pages., 1935; 9 (Reel 18)
  May 20, 1935. Opinion by George Sutherland; Minority Opinion by Benjamin Cardoza (Syllabus by Editorial Staff).
- 0293. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. Unidentified Fragment of Draft Document. 1 page., 10 (Reel 18)
- 0294. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. Correspondence and Petition of John H. Geer regarding the Almand-Hartsfield Bill to Define Sedition before the Georgia State Legislature. 2 pages., 1935; 11 (Reel 18)
- 0296. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. The Penal Code - Third Division: Crimes against the State and People, Georgia Code. 2 pages., 1926; 12 (Reel 18)
- 0298. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. Herndon v. Georgia United States Supreme Court. 14 pages., 1935; 13 (Reel 18)
- 0312. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. News clippings. 1 page., 1935; 14 (Reel 18)
- 0313. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. Herndon v. Georgia. United States Supreme Court. Drafts of Appellant's Statement of Jurisdiction. 28 pages., 15 (Reel 18)
- 0341. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. Superior Court of Fulton County, Georgia. Drafts of Petition for Writ of Habeas Corpus. 10 pages., 16 (Reel 18)
- 0351. Box 19/Folder f29. Angelo Herndon Case. Legal Documents. Herndon v. Georgia. Supreme Court. Memorandum for Plaintiff-in-error on Motion for Rehearing. 13 pages., 17 (Reel 18)
- 0364. Box 19/Folder f30. Angelo Herndon Case. Manuscripts. 70 pages., 1929-1936; 18 (Reel 18)
- 0434. Box 19/Folder f31. Angelo Herndon Case. Manuscripts. 74 pages., 1932-1936; 19 (Reel 18)
- 0508. Box 19/Folder f32. Angelo Herndon Case. 90 pages., 1932-1936; 20 (Reel 18)
- 0598. Box 20/Folder f33. Angelo Herndon Case. Angelo Herndon Writings - Newspaper Articles. 12 pages., 1934-1936; 21 (Reel 18)
- 0610. Box 20/Folder f34. Angelo Herndon Case. Angelo Herndon Writings - Pamphlets. 105 pages., 1934; 22 (Reel 18)
- 0715. Box 20/Folder f35. Angelo Herndon Case. Angelo Herndon Writings - Let Me Live (Book Reviews). 35 pages., 1937; 23 (Reel 18)
- 0740. Box 20/Folder f36. Angelo Herndon Case. Angelo Herndon Writings - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, Letters, etcetera. 67 pages., 1932-1935; 24 (Reel 18)
- 0807. Box 20/Folder f37. Angelo Herndon Case. Angelo Herndon Writings - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, Letters, etcetera. 76 pages., 1933-1935; 25 (Reel 18)
- 0883. Box 20/Folder g1. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. General. 126 pages., 1926; 26 (Reel 18)
  1926[1927]
- 1009. Box 20/Folder g2. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. International Labor Defense Bulletins and Press Releases. 25 pages., 1926-1928; 27 (Reel 18)
- 1034. Box 20/Folder g3. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. News clippings and General. 17 pages., 1926; 28 (Reel 18)
- 1051. Box 20/Folder g4. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. News clippings and General. 100 pages., 1926-1930; 29 (Reel 18)
- 1151. Box 20/Folder g5. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. News clippings and General. 38 pages., 1926-1930; 30 (Reel 18)
- 1189. Box 20/Folder g6. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Leaflets and Pamphlets. 44 pages., 1927-1928; 31 (Reel 18)
- 0001. Box 20/Folder g7. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Correspondence and News Clippings. 27 pages., 1926-1930; 1 (Reel 19)
- 0028. Box 20/Folder g8. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Telegrams. 105 pages., 1926-1927; 2 (Reel 19)
- 0029. Box 20/Folder g8. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Partial Transcript of Court Case Involving Arthur Garfield Hays as Counsel. 42 pages., 3 (Reel 19)
- 0071. Box 20/Folder g8. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Telegrams. 62 pages., 1926-1927; 4 (Reel 19)
- 0133. Box 20/Folder g9. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Press Releases, Articles, and Telegrams. 40 pages., 1926-1927; 5 (Reel 19)
  December 1926-May 1927
- 0173. Box 20/Folder g10. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. Emergency Committee Minutes and Reports. 49 pages., 1926-1927; 6 (Reel 19)
- 0222. Box 20/Folder g11. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. General. 91 pages., 1926-1927; 7 (Reel 19)
- 0313. Box 21/Folder g12. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. General. 93 pages., 1926-1927; 8 (Reel 19)
- 0406. Box 21/Folder g13. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. General. 49 pages., 1926-1927; 9 (Reel 19)
- 0455. Box 21/Folder g14. Sacco-Vanzetti Case. General. 79 pages., 1927-1928; 10 (Reel 19)
  1927[1928]
- 0534. Box 21/Folder h1. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. American Civil Liberties Union - Joint Committee on Workers Rights. 58 pages., 1934; 11 (Reel 19)
- 0592. Box 21/Folder h2. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. American Civil Liberties Union - Joint Committee on Workers Rights. 61 pages., 1934; 12 (Reel 19)
- 0653. Box 21/Folder h3. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. American Civil Liberties Union - Joint Committee on Workers Rights. 170 pages., 1938- 1940; 13 (Reel 19)
- 0823. Box 21/Folder h4. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. American Civil Liberties Union - Joint Committee on Workers Rights: Ratings of Cities. 13 pages., 1938-1939; 14 (Reel 19)
  [1938-]1939
- 0836. Box 21/Folder h5. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. American Civil Liberties Union - Joint Committee on Workers Rights. 70 pages., 1940- 1941; 15 (Reel 19)
- 0906. Box 21/Folder h6. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. American Civil Liberties Union - Joint Committee on Workers Rights. 52 pages., 1942; 16 (Reel 19)
- 0958. Box 21/Folder h7. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Berkman, Edith - Reports, Summaries, Biography, Interviews, Legal Material, etcetera. 115 pages., 1931-1932; 17 (Reel 19)
- 0960. Box 21/Folder h7. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Berkman, Edith - Berkman v. Tillinghast, United States Commissioner of Immigration. 44 pages., 1932; 18 (Reel 19)
  United States Supreme Court. Petition for Write of Certiorari and Brief in Support Thereof. October Term 1932.
- 1004. Box 21/Folder h7. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Berkman, Edith - Berkman v. Tillinghast, United States Commissioner of Immigration. 10 pages, 1932; 19 (Reel 19)
  United States Supreme Court. Application for Stay of Mandate and for Bail. October Term 1932
- 1014. Box 21/Folder h7. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Berkman, Edith - Berkman v. Tillinghast, United States Commissioner of Immigration. 59 pages., 1931; 20 (Reel 19)
  United States Court of Appeals for the First Circuit. Transcript of Record. October Term 1931.
- 1073. Box 21/Folder h8. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1948 - Vito Marcantonio. 182 pages., 1947-1948; 21 (Reel 19)
- 1255. Box 21/Folder h9. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1948 - Vito Marcantonio. 32 pages., 1947-1948; 22 (Reel 19)
- 0001. Box 22/Folder h10. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1950 - General news clippings. 119 pages., 1 (Reel 20)
- 0120. Box 22/Folder h10a. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1950 - General news clippings. 153 pages., 2 (Reel 20)
- 0273. Box 22/Folder h11. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1950 - Vito Marcantonio (Legislative Record, Leaflets, etcetera). 80 pages., 3 (Reel 20)
- 0353. Box 22/Folder h12. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1950 - Vito Marcantonio (Labor Petitions, etcetera). 17 pages., 4 (Reel 20)
- 0370. Box 22/Folder h13. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1950 - Vito Marcantonio (Literature). 200 pages., 1949-1950; 5 (Reel 20)
- 0570. Box 22/Folder h14. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Campaign 1950 - Vito Marcantonio (Press). 37 pages., 6 (Reel 20)
- 0607. Box 22/Folder h15. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Christian Front. 103 pages., 1939-1940; 7 (Reel 20)
  [1939-1940]
- 0710. Box 22/Folder h16. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Coughlin, Charles E. 136 pages., 1939-1940; 8 (Reel 20)
- 0846. Box 22/Folder h17. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Ford "Massacre" - News clippings. 102 pages., 1932; 9 (Reel 20)
- 0948. Box 22/Folder h18. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Gelders, Joseph S. Case. 113 pages., 1936-1937; 10 (Reel 20)
- 0001. Box 23/Folder h19. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Longo, John R. - New Jersey Supreme Court Transcripts. 136 pages., 1938; 1 (Reel 21)
  [1938]
- 0002. Box 23/Folder h19. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Longo, John R. - New Jersey versus Longo. New Jersey Supreme Court. Notice of Motion, Affidavit, and Brief in Support Thereof. 33 pages., 1938; 2 (Reel 21)
- 0035. Box 23/Folder h19. 0002. Box 23/Folder h19. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Longo, John R. - New Jersey versus Longo. New Jersey Supreme Court. Application for Writ of Certiorari. 29 pages., 1938; 3 (Reel 21)
- 0064. Box 23/Folder h19. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Longo, John R. - New Jersey v. Longo. New Jersey Supreme Court. State of Case on Writ of Error. 54 pages., 1938; 4 (Reel 21)
- 0118. Box 23/Folder h19. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Longo, John R. - New Jersey versus Longo. New Jersey Supreme Court. Notice of Motion, Affidavit, and Brief in Support Thereof. 19 pages., 1938; 5 (Reel 21)
- 0137. Box 23/Folder h20. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Longo, John R. - Photostats of Legal Documents [Fund Raising for Preparation of Appeal]. 14 pages., 1938; 6 (Reel 21)
- 0151. Box 23/Folder h21. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Minority Parties - Various States [Election Laws]. 89 pages., 1941; 7 (Reel 21)
  [1941]
- 0240. Box 23/Folder h22. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Minority Parties - Various States [Election Laws]. 109 pages., 1941; 8 (Reel 21)
- 0349. Box 23/Folder h23. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard. 70 pages., 1935-1937; 9 (Reel 21)
  File folder omitted. 1935-1936[1937]
- 0419. Box 23/Folder h24. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard. 19 pages., 1937-1938; 10 (Reel 21)
  1937[- 1938]
- 0438. Box 23/Folder h25. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard. 24 pages., 1938; 11 (Reel 21)
- 0462. Box 23/Folder h26. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Correspondence. 26 pages., 1938; 12 (Reel 21)
- 0488. Box 23/Folder h27. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Correspondence. 6 pages., 1938; 13 (Reel 21)
- 0494. Box 23/Folder h28. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Endorsements [of Bills]. 47 pages., 1938; 14 (Reel 21)
- 0541. Box 23/Folder h29. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Connery Bill. 6 pages., 1939; 15 (Reel 21)
- 0547. Box 23/Folder h30. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Bills. 48 pages., 1939; 16 (Reel 21)
- 0595. Box 23/Folder h31. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Correspondence. 40 pages., 1939; 17 (Reel 21)
- 0635. Box 23/Folder h32. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Correspondence. 58 pages., 1939; 18 (Reel 21)
- 0693. Box 23/Folder h33. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - Harlan, Kentucky. 36 pages., 1939; 19 (Reel 21)
- 0729. Box 24/Folder h34. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - General: Walter Wilson/David Scribner [Memoranda and Reports]. 120 pages., 1939; 20 (Reel 21)
- 0849. Box 24/Folder h35. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - General: Walter Wilson/David Scribner [Research Notes]. 159 pages., 1936- 1939; 21 (Reel 21)
  [1936-1939]
- 0001. Box 24/Folder h36. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. National Guard - General: Walter Wilson/David Scribner [Draft Report]. 66 pages., 1939; 1 (Reel 22)
  [1939]
- 0067. Box 24/Folder h37. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Oklahoma Case - [Criminal Syndicalist Cases]. 155 pages., 1940-1942; 2 (Reel 22)
- 0222. Box 24/Folder h38. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Parsons, Mrs. Lucy (Widow). 46 pages., 1939-1942; 3 (Reel 22)
  [1939-1942]
- 0268. Box 24/Folder h39. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. California. 95 pages., 1937-1938; 4 (Reel 22)
- 0285. Box 24/Folder h39. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. In the Matter of German Bulcke and V. Wahlenmaier. 76 pages., 1938; 5 (Reel 22)
  Superior Court of Los Angeles County, California. Order to Show Cause, Affidavits, Exhibits, Motion to Disqualify Judge, and Judgment in Contempt Proceedings [stemming from a dispute involving the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, the International Longshoremen's Association, and the Workers Alliance of San Diego, California].
- 0363. Box 24/Folder h40. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. [Report on the American Press]. 52 pages., 1950; 6 (Reel 22)
  [1950]
- 0415. Box 24/Folder h41. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. San Bernardino, California. 71 pages., 1937-1938; 7 (Reel 22)
- 0416. Box 24/Folder h41. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Coleman versus Johnson, et al. Superior Court of San Bernardino County, California. Complaint for Damages for Conspiracy [stemming from anti-union activities of city official and, 1937; 8 (Reel 22)
- 0486. Box 24/Folder h42. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. San Luis Obispo, California. 63 pages., 1936-1937; 9 (Reel 22)
  [1936-1937]
- 0495. Box 24/Folder h42. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. California versus Men salves and Bushnell. Superior Court of San Luis Obispo County, California. 2 pages., 1937; 10 (Reel 22)
  Affidavit [regarding preparation of documents in case involving Filipino Labor Union official and farm workers strike].
- 0518. Box 24/Folder h42. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. California versus Men salves and Bushnell. Superior Court of San Luis Obispo County, California. Court's Corrected Statement on Appeal. 31 pages., 1937; 11 (Reel 22)
- 0549. Box 24/Folder h43. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Twenty-Six Relief Pickets Case. 6 pages., 1938; 12 (Reel 22)
- 0551. Box 24/Folder h43. General Subject, Case, and Special Interest Files. Affidavits regarding Arrest of Unemployed Workers Picketing California State Relief Administration Headquarters in Los Angeles, California. 4 pages., 1938; 13 (Reel 22)
- 0555. General Subject and Special Interest Files. Louisiana - State Jim-Crow Legislation Affecting Public Transportation. 1 page., 1928-1944; 14 (Reel 22)
- 0556. General Subject and Special Interest Files. International Workers Order [IWO] and International Labor Defense [ILD]. 77 pages., 1944-1947; 15 (Reel 22)
  1944 and 1947
- 0557. General Subject and Special Interest Files. International Workers Order Press Releases. 38 pages., 1947; 16 (Reel 22)
  January-July 1947
- 0594. General Subject and Special Interest Files. "Equal Justice and Democracy in the Service of Victory: Continuing the Work of Anna Damon," by the International Labor Defense. 31 pages., 1944; 17 (Reel 22)
- 0625. General Subject and Special Interest Files. International Labor Defense Leader. 8 pages., 1935; 18 (Reel 22)
- 0633. General Subject and Special Interest Files. International Labor Defense [ILD] and Congress of Industrial Organizations [CIO]. 74 pages., 1941-1944; 19 (Reel 22)
  1942[1941-1944]
- 0634. General Subject and Special Interest Files. "For Victory: Support for the President's Policies for National Unity - An Open Letter to President Roosevelt from 800 United States Civic and Labor Leaders," by the International Labor Defense. 11 pages., 1942; 20 (Reel 22)
- 0664. General Subject and Special Interest Files. "Remember Pearl Harbor!: Defense Migration and Labor Supply," by Howard B. Myers, Works Progress Administration. 7 pages., 1941; 21 (Reel 22)
  December 29, 1941
- 0671. General Subject and Special Interest Files. Congress of Industrial Organizations and Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Press Releases and Bulletins. 36 pages., 1942; 22 (Reel 22)
- 0707. General Subject and Special Interest Files. National Association of Colored Graduate Nurses. 7 pages., 1945; 23 (Reel 22)
- 0712. General Subject and Special Interest Files. International Labor Defense and National Negro Congress. 36 pages., 1941-1942; 24 (Reel 22)
- 0748. General Subject and Special Interest Files. International Labor Defense Legislative and Information Service. 58 pages., 1945; 25 (Reel 22)
- 0806. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General. 115 pages., 1933- 1938; 26 (Reel 22)
  [1933-1938]
- 0812. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - "Rule of the Supreme Court of Georgia." 8 pages., 1934; 27 (Reel 22)
- 0825. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Fragment of Unidentified Draft Brief on Federal Questions. 6 pages., 28 (Reel 22)
- 0831. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Lowry versus Herndon. Georgia Supreme Court. Opinion by Justice Atkinson. 6 pages., 1936; 29 (Reel 22)
- 0837. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Herndon versus Georgia. 4 pages., 1934; 30 (Reel 22)
  United States Supreme Court. Statement of Points on Which the Appellant Intends to Rely and Designation of Portions of the Record Necessary for the Consideration of the Same. October Term 1934.
- 0841. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Herndon versus Georgia. 26 pages., 1933; 31 (Reel 22)
  Georgia Supreme Court. Defendant's Reply Brief.
- 0867. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Herndon versus Georgia. 7 pages., 1934; 32 (Reel 22)
  Georgia Supreme Court. Motion for Rehearing.
- 0874. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Herndon versus Georgia. 3 pages., 1934; 33 (Reel 22)
  Georgia Supreme Court. Certificate. July 1934
- 0877. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Herndon versus Georgia. 13 pages., 1934; 34 (Reel 22)
  Georgia Supreme Court. Petition. August 12, 1934
- 0890. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Herndon versus Georgia. 2 pages., 1934; 35 (Reel 22)
  Georgia Supreme Court. Stay of Execution. July 31, 1934.
- 0897. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Georgia v. Herndon. 3 pages., 1934; 36 (Reel 22)
  Superior Court of Fulton County, Georgia. Indictment and Conviction for Attempting to Incite Insurrection and Circulating Insurrectionary Literature. August 4, 1934.
- 0900. Additional Material Filed Separately from International Labor Defense Papers. Angelo Herndon Case Record Group SCM 78-33. Legal and General - Points for Letter to Chief Justice Russell and Herndon Case Notes. 12 pages., 37 (Reel 22)